Marc Brown Papers MS148
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Arthur print material, 1994 -- 2007; 1994 -- 2000; MS148.001; 49 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s) Disk image available for reading room access.
  - 46B: How the cookie crumbles, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.008.00046 (Box 8)
  - 46B: How the cookie crumbles, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.008.00047 (Box 8)
  - 46B: How the cookie crumbles, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.008.00048 (Box 8)
  - 47A: Arthur vs. the very mean crossing guard, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.008.00049 (Box 8)
  - 47A: Arthur vs. the very mean crossing guard, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.008.00050 (Box 8)
  - 47A: Arthur vs. the very mean crossing guard, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.008.00051 (Box 8)
  - 47A: Arthur vs. the very mean crossing guard, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.008.00052 (Box 8)
  - 47A: Arthur vs. the very mean crossing guard, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.008.00053 (Box 8)
  - 47A: Arthur vs. the very mean crossing guard; 47B: Sue Ellen's little sister, notes on sound, music, and animation, 1997; MS148.001.008.00054 (Box 8)
  - 47B: Sue Ellen's little sister, location designs/backgrounds and background log, 1997; MS148.001.008.00055 (Box 8)
  - 47B: Sue Ellen's little sister, incidental character model package and model sheet, 1997; MS148.001.008.00056 (Box 8)
  - 47B: Sue Ellen's little sister, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.008.00057 (Box 8)
  - 47B: Sue Ellen's little sister, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.008.00058 (Box 8)
  - 47B: Sue Ellen's little sister, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.008.00059 (Box 8)
  - 47B: Sue Ellen's little sister, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.008.00060 (Box 8)
  - 47B: Sue Ellen's little sister, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.008.00061 (Box 8)
  - 48A: Love notes for Muffy, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.008.00062 (Box 8)
  - 48A: Love notes for Muffy, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.008.00063 (Box 8)
  - 48A: Love notes for Muffy, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.008.00064 (Box 8)
  - 48A: Love notes for Muffy, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.008.00065 (Box 8)
  - 48A: Love notes for Muffy, 48B: Arthur the loser, notes on sound, music, and animation, 1997; MS148.001.008.00066 (Box 8)
  - 48B: Arthur the loser, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.008.00067 (Box 8)
  - 48B: Arthur the loser, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.008.00068 (Box 8)
  - 48B: Arthur the loser, location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.008.00069 (Box 8)
  - 48B: Arthur the loser, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - 49A: D.W.'s very bad mood, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - 49A: D.W.'s very bad mood, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - 49A: D.W.'s very bad mood, location designs/ backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - 49A: D.W.'s very bad mood, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - 49A: D.W.'s very bad mood, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - 49A: D.W.'s very bad mood; 49B: Finders key-pers, notes on music, 1997; MS148.001.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - 49B: Finders key-pers, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - 49B: Finders key-pers, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - 49B: Finders key-pers, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - 49B: Finders key-pers, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - 49B: Finders key-pers, location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - 50A: D.W. blows the whistle, 50B: Buster hits the books, notes on sound, music, and animation, 1997; MS148.001.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - 50A: D.W. blows the whistle, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - 50A: D.W. blows the whistle, location designs/ backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - 50A: D.W. blows the whistle, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - 50A: D.W. blows the whistle, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - 50B: Buster hits the books, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - 50B: Buster hits the books, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - 50B: Buster hits the books, location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - 50B: Buster hits the books, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - 50B: Buster hits the books, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - 51A: Binky rules, incidental character model package and model sheet, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - 51A: Binky rules, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - 51A: Binky rules, location designs/backgrounds, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - 51A: Binky rules, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - 51A: Binky rules, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - 51A: Binky rules, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - 51A: Binky rules, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - 51A: Binky rules, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - 51A: Binky rules, script, final draft, 1997; MS148.001.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - 51B: Buster's back, script, final draft, 1997; MS148.001.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - 51B: Buster's back, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - 51B: Buster's back, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - 51B: Buster's back, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - 51B: Buster's back, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - 51B: Buster's back, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - 51B: Buster's back, incidental character model package, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00038 (Box 9)
  - 51B: Buster's back, location designs/backgrounds, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - 51B: Buster's back, oversized location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - 52A: The ballad of Buster Baxter, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - 52A: The ballad of Buster Baxter, script, third draft, 1997; MS148.001.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - 52A: The ballad of Buster Baxter, location design/backgrounds and background log, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00043 (Box 9)
  - 52A: The ballad of Buster Baxter, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.009.00044 (Box 9)
  - 52A: The ballad of Buster Baxter, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.009.00045 (Box 9)
  - 52A: The ballad of Buster Baxter, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00046 (Box 9)
  - 52A: The ballad of Buster Baxter, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.009.00047 (Box 9)
  - 52A: The ballad of Buster Baxter, notes on sound, music, and animation, 1997; MS148.001.009.00048 (Box 9)
  - 52A: The ballad of Buster Baxter, sketch of moose minstrel, comments, 1997; MS148.001.009.00049 (Box 9)
  - 52A: The ballad of Buster Baxter, incidental character model package and model sheet, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00050 (Box 9)
  - 52B: Arthur rides the bandwagon, script, first draft, 1997; MS148.001.009.00051 (Box 9)
  - 52B: Arthur rides the bandwagon, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.009.00052 (Box 9)
  - 52B: Arthur rides the bandwagon, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.009.00053 (Box 9)
  - 52B: Arthur rides the bandwagon, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.009.00054 (Box 9)
  - 52B: Arthur rides the bandwagon, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.009.00055 (Box 9)
  - 52B: Arthur rides the bandwagon, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00056 (Box 9)
  - 52B: Arthur rides the bandwagon, incidental character model package, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00057 (Box 9)
  - 52B: Arthur rides the bandwagon, location designs/backgrounds and background log, final, 1997; MS148.001.009.00058 (Box 9)
  - 53A: Arthur goes crosswire, script, first draft, 1997; MS148.001.009.00059 (Box 9)
  - 53A: Arthur goes crosswire, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.009.00060 (Box 9)
  - 53A: Arthur goes crosswire, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - 53A: Arthur goes crosswire, incidental character model package, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - 53A: Arthur goes crosswire, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - 53A: Arthur goes crosswire; 53B: Background blues, notes on sound and animation, 1997; MS148.001.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - 53B: Background blues, script, first draft, 1997; MS148.001.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - 53B: Background blues, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - 53B: Background blues, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - 53B: Background blues, location designs/backgrounds and background log, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - 53B: Background blues, incidental character model package, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - 53B: Background blues, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - 53B: Background blues, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - 54A: Arthur's treasure hunt, script, first draft, 1997; MS148.001.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - 54A: Arthur's treasure hunt, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - 54A: Arthur's treasure hunt, incidental character model package, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - 54A: Arthur's treasure hunt, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - 54A: Arthur's treasure hunt, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - 54A: Arthur's treasure hunt, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - 54A: Arthur's treasure hunt, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - 54A: Arthur's treasure hunt, location designs/backgrounds, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - 54A: Arthur's treasure hunt; 54B: The chips are down, notes on sound, music, and animation, 1997; MS148.001.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - 54B: The chips are down, location designs/backgrounds, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - 54B: The chips are down, incidental character model package, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - 54B: The chips are down, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - 54B: The chips are down, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - 54B: The chips are down, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - 54B: The chips are down, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - 54B: The chips are down, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - 54B: The chips are down, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.010.00028 (Box 10)
  - 55A: Meet Binky, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00029 (Box 10)
  - 55A: Meet Binky, location designs/ backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00030 (Box 10)
  - 55A: Meet Binky, incidental character model package, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00031 (Box 10)
  - 55A: Meet Binky, location designs/backgrounds, final., 1997; MS148.001.010.00032 (Box 10)
  - 55A: Meet Binky, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00033 (Box 10)
  - 55A: Meet Binky, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.010.00034 (Box 10)
  - 55B: I'd rather read it myself, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00035 (Box 10)
  - 55B: I'd rather read it myself, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00036 (Box 10)
  - 55B: I'd rather read it myself, incidental character model package, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00037 (Box 10)
  - 55B: I'd rather read it myself, location designs/backgrounds, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00038 (Box 10)
  - 55B: I'd rather read it myself, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00039 (Box 10)
  - 55B: I'd rather read it myself, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.010.00040 (Box 10)
  - 56A: Revenge of the chip, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00041 (Box 10)
  - 56A: Revenge of the chip, location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.010.00042 (Box 10)
  - 56A: Revenge of the chip, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.010.00043 (Box 10)
  - 56A: Revenge of the chip, location designs/ backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00044 (Box 10)
  - 56A: Revenge of the chip, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00045 (Box 10)
  - 56A: Revenge of the chip, script, first draft, 1997; MS148.001.010.00046 (Box 10)
  - 56A: Revenge of the chip, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.010.00047 (Box 10)
  - 56A: Revenge of the chip; 56B: D.W., all fired up; 59A: Dad's dessert dilemma; 59B: Arthur's dummy disaster, notes on sound, music, and animation, 1997; MS148.001.010.00048 (Box 10)
  - 56B: D.W., all fired up, main/incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.010.00049 (Box 10)
  - 56B: D.W., all fired up, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00050 (Box 10)
  - 56B: D.W., all fired up, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00051 (Box 10)
  - 56B: D.W., all fired up, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00052 (Box 10)
  - 56B: D.W., all fired up, location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.010.00053 (Box 10)
  - 56B: D.W., all fired up, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.010.00054 (Box 10)
  - 57A: Popular girls, incidental character mode package, 1997; MS148.001.010.00055 (Box 10)
  - 57A: Popular girls, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.010.00056 (Box 10)
  - 57A: Popular girls, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00057 (Box 10)
  - 57A: Popular girls, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.010.00058 (Box 10)
  - 57A: Popular girls, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.010.00059 (Box 10)
  - 57B: Sue Ellen and the brainasaurous, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.010.00060 (Box 10)
  - 57B: Sue Ellen and the brainasaurous, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.010.00061 (Box 10)
  - 57B: Sue Ellen and the brainasaurous, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00062 (Box 10)
  - 57B: Sue Ellen and the brainasaurous, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.010.00063 (Box 10)
  - 57B: Sue Ellen and the brainasaurous, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.010.00064 (Box 10)
  - 57B: Sue Ellen and the brainasaurous, location design/background, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00065 (Box 10)
  - 58A: Attack of the turbo Tibbles, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.010.00066 (Box 10)
  - 58A: Attack of the turbo Tibbles, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.010.00067 (Box 10)
  - 58A: Attack of the turbo Tibbles, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.010.00068 (Box 10)
  - 58A: Attack of the turbo Tibbles, backgrounds, colors, 1997; MS148.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - 58A: Attack of the turbo Tibbles, script, second draft, 1998; MS148.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - 58B: And now let's talk to some kids, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - 58B: And now let's talk to some kids, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - 58B: And now let's talk to some kids, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - 58B: And now let's talk to some kids, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - 58B: And now let's talk to some kids, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - 58B: And now let's talk to some kids, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - 59A: Dad's dessert dilemma, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - 59A: Dad's dessert dilemma, incidental character model package, final, 1997; MS148.001.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - 59A: Dad's dessert dilemma, location designs/backgrounds, final, 1997; MS148.001.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - 59A: Dad's dessert dilemma, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - 59A: Dad's dessert dilemma, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - 59A: Dad's dessert dilemma, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - 59A: Dad's dessert dilemma, script, first draft, 1997; MS148.001.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - 59A: Dad's dessert dilemma, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - 59B: Arthur's dummy disaster, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - 59B: Arthur's dummy disaster, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - 59B: Arthur's dummy disaster, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - 59B: Arthur's dummy disaster, script, second draft, 1998; MS148.001.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - 59B: Arthur's dummy disaster, incidental character model package, final, 1997; MS148.001.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - 59B: Arthur's dummy disaster, location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - 60A: D.W. tricks the Tooth Fairy, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - 60A: D.W. tricks the Tooth Fairy, location designs/backgrounds, final, 1997; MS148.001.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - 60A: D.W. tricks the Tooth Fairy, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - 60A: D.W. tricks the Tooth Fairy, incidental character model package, final, 1997; MS148.001.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - 60A: D.W. tricks the Tooth Fairy, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - 60A: D.W. tricks the Tooth Fairy, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - 60A: D.W. tricks the Tooth Fairy, script, second draft, 1998; MS148.001.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - 60A: D.W. tricks the Tooth Fairy; 60B: Buster's growing grudge, notes on sound, music, and animation, 1998; MS148.001.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - 60B: Buster's growing grudge, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00031 (Box 11)
  - 60B: Buster's growing grudge, location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.011.00032 (Box 11)
  - 60B: Buster's growing grudge, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.011.00033 (Box 11)
  - 60B: Buster's growing grudge, background, color, 1997; MS148.001.011.00034 (Box 11)
  - 60B: Buster's growing grudge, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.011.00035 (Box 11)
  - 60B: Buster's growing grudge, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00036 (Box 11)
  - 60B: Buster's growing grudge, storyboard, rough, 1997; MS148.001.011.00037 (Box 11)
  - 60B: Buster's growing grudge, script, second draft, 1998; MS148.001.011.00038 (Box 11)
  - 61A: Francine and the feline, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00039 (Box 11)
  - 61A: Francine and the feline, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.011.00040 (Box 11)
  - 61A: Francine and the feline, storyboard, final, 1998; MS148.001.011.00041 (Box 11)
  - 61A: Francine and the feline, revised sketches of Nemo the cat, notes, 1998; MS148.001.011.00042 (Box 11)
  - 61A: Francine and the feline, location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.011.00043 (Box 11)
  - 61A: Francine and the feline, script, second draft, 1998; MS148.001.011.00044 (Box 11)
  - 61B: The return of the king, location designs/backgrounds, rough, 1997; MS148.001.011.00045 (Box 11)
  - 61B: The return of the king, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.011.00046 (Box 11)
  - 61B: The return of the King, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.011.00047 (Box 11)
  - 61B: The return of the king, storyboard, final, 1997; MS148.001.011.00048 (Box 11)
  - 61B: The return of the king, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00049 (Box 11)
  - 61B: The return of the king, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.011.00050 (Box 11)
  - 61B: The return of the king, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.011.00051 (Box 11)
  - 62A: The long, dull winter, script, second draft, 1998; MS148.001.011.00052 (Box 11)
  - 62A: The long, dull winter, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00053 (Box 11)
  - 62A: The long, dull winter, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.011.00054 (Box 11)
  - 62A: The long, dull winter, location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.011.00055 (Box 11)
  - 62A: The long, dull winter, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.011.00056 (Box 11)
  - 62A: The long, dull winter, storyboard, final, 1998; MS148.001.011.00057 (Box 11)
  - 62A: The long, dull winter; 62B: What scared Sue Ellen?, notes on sound, music, and animation, 1997; MS148.001.011.00058 (Box 11)
  - 62B: What scared Sue Ellen?, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00059 (Box 11)
  - 62B: What scared Sue Ellen?, script, second draft, 1998; MS148.001.011.00060 (Box 11)
  - 62B: What scared Sue Ellen?, storyboard, final, 1998; MS148.001.011.00061 (Box 11)
  - 62B: What scared Sue Ellen?, location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.011.00062 (Box 11)
  - 62B: What scared Sue Ellen?, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.011.00063 (Box 11)
  - 62B: What scared Sue Ellen?, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.011.00064 (Box 11)
  - 62B: What scared Sue Ellen?, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.011.00065 (Box 11)
  - 63A: Mom and Dad have a great big fight, script, second draft, 1998; MS148.001.011.00066 (Box 11)
  - 63A: Mom and Dad have a great big fight, storyboard, final, 1998; MS148.001.011.00067 (Box 11)
  - 63A: Mom and Dad have a great big fight, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.011.00068 (Box 11)
  - 63A: Mom and Dad have a great big fight, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00069 (Box 11)
  - 63A: Mom and Dad have a great big fight; 63B: Clarissa is cracked, notes on music, 1997; MS148.001.011.00070 (Box 11)
  - 63B: Clarissa is cracked, location designs/backgrounds, 1997; MS148.001.011.00071 (Box 11)
  - 63B: Clarissa is cracked, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.011.00072 (Box 11)
  - 63B: Clarissa is cracked, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.011.00073 (Box 11)
  - 63B: Clarissa is cracked, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.011.00074 (Box 11)
  - 63B: Clarissa is cracked, storyboard, final, 1998; MS148.001.011.00075 (Box 11)
  - 63B: Clarissa is cracked, script, second draft, 1997; MS148.001.011.00076 (Box 11)
  - 64A: D.W.'s perfect wish, incidental character model package, rough, 1997; MS148.001.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - 64A: D.W.'s perfect wish, storyboard, final, 1998; MS148.001.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - 64A: D.W.'s perfect wish, incidental character model package with color models, 1997; MS148.001.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - 64A: D.W.'s perfect wish, incidental character model package, 1997; MS148.001.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - 64A: D.W.'s perfect wish; 64B: Arthur and D.W. clean up!, notes on animation and music, 1997; MS148.001.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - 64B: Arthur and D.W. clean up, script, second draft, 1998; MS148.001.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - 64B: Arthur and D.W. clean up, backgrounds, color, 1997; MS148.001.012.00007 (Box 12)